maxviral.com 2017-11-16

# Privacy Policy - MaxViral

## MaxViral.com (hereinafter “MV”, “MaxViral”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) adopts policies and procedures on the treatment of personally identifiable information (hereinafter “Personal Information”) collected, directly or indirectly, when you are accessing or using www.maxviral.com (hereinafter “Site”) or our services, features, content or applications (collectively with the Site, the “Services”).

* * *

## Can I refuse to be bound by this Privacy Policy?

By using the Services, you are consenting to the collection, manipulation, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of Personal Information, by MV or our business partners, as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Why do we collect Personal Information?

We want to offer you always the most tailored and updated service available. It may require us to collect, use, share, and/or display some of your Personal Information.

## What kind of information do we collect?

We collect the following types of information:

**Account Information:**

By creating an Account on the Services you provide us with Personal Information (for instance, username, password and email address, etc.). If you access the Services through Facebook credentials, we may automatically collect certain information available through Facebook, such as your name, picture, and email address, and use them in accordance with Facebook’s policies.

**User Content:**

Your comments and all content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by MV and we may continue to disclose such content to third parties, even after you terminate your Account.

**Information Collected Automatically:**

in order to fight spam/malware, to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services, and to custom, improve and keep on the Services, some information from your device or web browser such as IP addresses, online activities, cookies or others, are received and recorded automatically when you interact with the Services.

To enable us and our business partners to improve our Services we need to figure out how often users access it. It means that some usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site or mobile application, are automatically collected and may be used in aggregate form for statistical purposes.

It is possible to opt-out only of data collection on the links you have shared with others. Please get in touch with us to learn more.

**Location Data:**

Your geo-location data may also be collected by our Services to provide location-related functionality. You may adjust your location services settings to stop sharing your location data with us.

**Email Communications:**

To improve our Services and customer service we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.

## Information Collected Using Cookies:

Cookies are stored by your web browser when you visit a website and associates them. We use cookies to know how and when you use and share our the Services.

There are other ways we may use cookies: to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and associate that information with your Account, the device you use, the email or social media accounts that you use to connect to our Services and to share our content.

You are free to turn off the cookie feature on your browser. However we strongly recommend that you leave cookies active on your browser, because they enable you to take advantage of the best features of the Services.

Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and not the use by third parties.

## Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons:

Advertisements supports and enhances our Services, they may be sometimes targeted and served to particular users who fit a certain general profile category that may be inferred from information provided to us by a user, may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third Party Services. Advertisements may come from third party companies, such as ad servers or ad agencies. They may collect information about your online activities when you use our Services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these ad networks and other parties.

## Do you share my Personal Information?

The content you have posted or shared publicly through our Services, such as posts, comments, or other submissions is public by default.

Please note that, by using our certain public features, you may choose to provide Personal Information publicly available. In this way you may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information.

User profile information may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services. User email addresses will not be revealed to other users of our Site.

In order to provide you some of our Services we may need to share Personal Information with our service providers that, however, are not authorized to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

## Does this Privacy Policy apply to third parties?

Please note that this Privacy Policy only governs information we collect in connection with the Services and does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (hereinafter “Third Party Services”).

You may access other Third Party services or sites through the Services, by accessing through them to the Service or clicking on links on the Site. Therefore we encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

## Will you use my Personal Information for email marketing?

Your email address may be occasionally used by MV to send emails and other communications to you, such as those related to your Account and for purposes important to the Services, such as password recovery. We may also use your contact information to contact you for editorial and marketing purposes. You may choose to unsubscribe from commercial emails you receive from us, but not from the service-related information, such as password recovery.

## Will my information be disclosed pursuant to business transfers?

Personal Information would be one of the assets that is transferred in the case we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy. Following the transfer of user information in the circumstances described in this paragraph, all inquiries concerning the processing of user information should be directed to the entity to which the information is transferred.

## Are there information that may be disclosed for your protection or the protection of others?

Please note that MaxViral reserves the right al all time to access, read and disclose any information as necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law or regulation, legal prosecution or governmental request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Service, or (iii) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This may include exchanging information with third parties for spam/ malware prevention and fraud protection.

## Is my Private Information secure?

For your privacy and security reasons your Account information will be protected by a password that is your due to keep private and protect appropriately in order to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information.

We use techniques reasonably designed to secure the information. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information, nor we do guarantee the security of any Account.

Despite your and our cautions, hardware or software failure, unauthorized entry or use, and other causes, may compromise the security at any time.

## What information of mine can I access?

You can access and delete cookies through your web browser settings. Furthermore, registered users can access their information by logging into their Account.

## Can I delete my account?

Yes, you can delete your account by emailing hello@maxviral.com. Please note that Account termination implies that any information you provided will no longer be accessible via your Account and that any your public activity prior to deletion will remain stored by on our serves and may be publicly accessible.

## What happens if you amend this Privacy Policy?

All changes to this Privacy Policy will be notified you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. The collected information is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used, what implies that a user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted on the Site.

## What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

Please feel free to send us an email to hello@maxviral.com for any questions or concerns you may have regarding this Privacy Policy.
